[
	{
		"question": "Game question: What year was among us made? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["2018"]
  },
  	{
		"question": "Security question: What is a thing that you should NERVER share with anybody at all time about your account as of 2022? [Say the one you think it is: password, email, 2fa, token] (Medium)",
		"answers": ["token"]
  },
  	{
		"question": "Security question: Which one is more safe? http or https (Medium)",
		"answers": ["https"]
  },
  {
  		"question": "Normal question: How many letters are there in the english alphabet? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["26!"]
    },
          {
  		"question": "Game question: What year was Classic: Crossroads made by Roblox? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["2007"]
    },
    {
    		"question": "Dev question: Who is the creator of this bot? (A bit easy)",
		"answers": ["adudu21", "Hecker",  "Hecker#1844"]
    }, 
    {
    		"question": "Dev question: What year was this bot made? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["2022"]
        },
    {
    		"question": "Game question: What year was Friday Night Funkin made? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["2020"]
        },
     {
         		"question": "Youtube question: What year was the channel of MrBeast Made? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["2012"]
     },
          {
         		"question": "Game question: Who made FE2/Flood escape 2 on roblox? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["Crazyblox"]
     },
    
                {
         		"question": "Normal question: Are cats bigger than humans normaly? (Normal)",
		"answers": ["no!"]
     },
                     {
         		"question": "Youtube question: Does mrbeast have over 2+ channels? (Normal)",
		"answers": ["yes"]
     },
                     {
         		"question": "internet question: Does google collect data? (Easy)",
		"answers": ["yes"]
     },
                     {
         		"question": "Game question: On roblox are you able to see your moderation history?",
		"answers": ["yes"]
     },
                     {
         		"question": "Normal question: Are dogs bigger than humans normaly?",
		"answers": ["no!"]
     },
     {
          		"question": "Game question: What is the name of the first ever roblox group? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["RobloHunks"]
    },
    {
    		"question": "Game question: Who is the CEO of roblox in 2022? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["David Baszucki"]
            },
            {
                		"question": "Game question: Was there a beta version of roblox, if so then what was the name? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["DynaBlocks"]
            },
     {
    		"question": "Discord question: What was the most popular server on discord in 2022? (Medium)",
		"answers": ["mid journey"]
  },
       {
    		"question": "Math question: What is 2039x3x0? (Easy)",
		"answers": ["0"]
  },
{
    		"question": "Math question: What is 5x5? (Easy)",
		"answers": ["25!"]
}
]
